Coordonnées

+79960656823 (Mobile) tondjilee@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/lee-tondji-niat (LinkedIn)

tnjl.herokuapp.com (Company)

Principales compétences

Programmation web
Gestion de projet
Développement site web

Languages

English (Professional Working)
French (Native or Bilingual)
Italian (Professional Working)

Certifications

Microfrontends with React: A Complete Developer's Guide

React

PHP

Front End Libraries

Lee TONDJI NIAT

Lead Frontend developer

Nijni-Novgorod

Résumé

I'm a software engineer and also a designer enthousiast. I really like to create and learn new things. My main goal everyday is to learn something new and improve my skills as ever. I'm specialized in web application especially with React (Typescript), Node.js, Nest.js, GraphQL, and more

I can talk about technologies, programming in general during a whole day, so I would be glad to talk with you or others to share and learn more.

Expérience

TSN

Lead Frontend developer décembre 2020 - Present (1 an)

Russie

web mechanica Fullstack Developer juillet 2020 - décembre 2020 (6 mois) Nijni-Novgorod, Russie

Freea Co Lead Frontend Developer février 2020 - août 2020 (7 mois) Nijni-Novgorod, Nijni-Novgorod, Russie

Indépendant Web & mobile consultant @ Lyss Consulting décembre 2017 - juillet 2020 (2 ans 8 mois)

Douala

Programactor Web Developer juin 2016 - décembre 2017 (1 an 7 mois) Douala, Logbessou

Freelance

SMART

Web developer janvier 2016 - décembre 2017 (2 ans) Douala

Freelance

Kumity

Java/Java EE Developer mars 2017 - août 2017 (6 mois)

Cameroun

JUBENROS

Project manager septembre 2016 - octobre 2016 (2 mois)

Douala, Bonamoussadi

Inducted as a project manager for the management of a team of developers in order to provide JUBENROS SARL with a web application for the management of their truck fleet. This for a period of one month.

JUBENROS

analyst programmer septembre 2014 - janvier 2015 (5 mois)

Douala

The development of management applications for different structures of the place and also utilities that can improve the daily life of JUBENROS SARL employees.

CMT

web developer 2015 - 2015 (moins d'un an)

Feu rouge

Implement web and mobile applications

Formation

Нижегородский Государственный Университет им. Н.И. Лобачевского (ННГУ)

Bachelor's degree, Technologie informatique / technologie des systèmes informatiques · (2019)

CS2I Lorient

Bachelor, Information system design · (2015 - 2016)

Collège communautaire du Nouveau-Brunswick (CCNB)

Diploma of College Studies, Analyst programmer · (2012 - 2013)